I will say everything once again. The main purpose of my discussion was that monthly income...
I mean, first of all, I said that the values here should already be met.
I mean, I was looking at this tool.
Then I felt that we had such a discussion on civility or on property.
What is in my mind?
Actually, if I am thinking about home loans and I am trying to find the best deals...
Actually, I don't want you to tell me what the best parameters should be.
If you tell me that I will get a loan of Rs. 750,000, I will give it to you in six months.
I will take a small loan and it will be perfect.
I will find a credit agency that will let me increase my credit score.
If you tell me that salary is more than self-employed, then I will remove my pay slip.
I have been doing this for six months.
You told me that 30 years of age is not good.
My wife is 28 years old.
I will take her name.
I don't want to have a loan that is perfect for me.
I want you to save Rs. 400,000 even if you have a high civil score.
If you have taken your wife's name, then you have saved Rs. 400,000.